Dafna Pundak

Full-Stack Web Developer

Profile

I have been working as a personal assistant and operations for almost five years. During this period, I graduated my first and second degree. Now I am placing all my efforts in building my web developing career. Although successful in my previous career, I have realized that the aspects of work I find most exciting are all in the code writing world:

- Highly organized and down to details worker my work as a personal assistant, required developed multitasking skills, time and schedule management, and prioritization of tasks.
- Endless motivation for learning during my military service, academic studies or web developer boot-camp, not once was I required to study and master a new field of knowledge on my own. Every time I faced such new challenge, I did it with much eagerness, passion and joy.
- Excellent interpersonal and team working skills serving as an operations
 officer, I planned, coordinated and led end-to-end global operations which
 required cooperation between different departments, units and
 organizations. I have always felt that the people I have came across with,
 enjoyed and valued working with me.

Projects

Weather App

A full stack application using OOP and MVC design, access an external API from my server, and save data to a database with CRUD operations.

Bank App

A MERN stack application.

Education

Full Stack Web Developer, Elevation, Tel Aviv

November 2019 — January 2020

- An industry-based intensive 3-month coding Bootcamp which covered the entire MERN stack and beyond.
- Built a number of end-to-end projects from scratch while adhering to solid OOP principles and communicating with a number of external APIs.

M.B.A, Bar-Ilan University

2017 — 2019

 Master of Business Administration Specializing in Management and Organizational Behavior.

B.Sc, Hebrew University of Jerusalem,

2015 - 2017

• Bachelor of Science in Environmental Economics and Management. Graduated with Excellency (Grade 92.03).

Employment History

Personal assistant and office manager at Una Dance Academy, Tel Aviv

2017 — 2019

- · Sales and marketing.
- Bookkeeping and finance consultancy.
- Planned and led an organized sale process. This resulted a large increase in revenue and effective handling of customer payments.

Pilates instructor, Kibutz Na'an

2017 — 2018

Operations officer at Intelligence Corps, IDF

2010 — 2014

- Served and commanded as a First Lieutenant at an Elite Unit in the Intelligence corps.
- Led end-to-end projects, from planning to execution.
- Managed project timelines and built gantt charts.
- Excellency certificate given by unit commander.

Details

Tel Aviv, Israel, +972 524536478

dafna.m88@gmail.com

Links

Portfolio LinkedIn

Skills

JavaScript (ES5/6) HTML/CSS

React

jQuery

Node.js

Express

MongoDB

Mongoose

Languages

Hebrew

English